I made coffee before the stream.
No need to, you know, what's happening?
Why are you guys going?
Get back here.
Trying to sneak out on me.
What's going on?
Ah, man.
How's it going, huh?
Does he know?
Does I know what?
I know all the things.
So whatever your question is, yes, I know.
I know it all.
I've seen it.
What the fuck is going on with the grocery store stories, and I have no idea what you're talking about.
You, Mr. Nazina?
I actually... what are you talking about?
First time in the stream?
Hey, what's up?
Usually only watch old MC VODs.
Hope you chat.
Have a great time.
Thank you very much, KRZ.
I'm gonna have a fantastic time.
I'm trying to, you know, put a damper on my excitement, but I kind of want to scream.
Because I can't wait to play.
But I'm trying to keep it down, you know?
Any greed today?
Maybe.
We'll see.
I'm definitely gonna roll the dice, though.
I'm gonna fucking, you know, spin the wheel and see what we get.
Which character?
Don't fall your sparkle?
I don't know what that means.
This is the guy who invented the Lumina converter.
That's such an old one.
Well, not for you guys, I guess.
I invented the knife.
You're confusing me with someone else.
I did the knife.
Lumina converter is someone else.
Planning a vacation in Denmark.
Any recommendations to visit?
If you like hiking a little bit, or maybe bicycling, I would suggest renting a bicycle and going on a trip along the western coast of Schele, which is the eastern island part of Denmark.
It's amazing there.
It is such a good time in the summer.
And you stop by all these quaint towns on the way near the water, you get an ice cream, you enjoy the sun, and you keep riding the bicycle.
It's fantastic.
Or you go to Jülen, to Molspieu, which is like a national park.
I recommend that, too.
It's pretty cool.
There's just cows there.
You can pet them as you hike.
It's amazing.
Other than that, I don't know, just Copenhagen, I guess, during the summer is quite fantastic.
I'm seeking your streams every day, don't hold back.
Okay.
You know, that's good you're saying it, because I am actually holding back a little bit.
I'm not kidding.
Like, I want to stream more and play this game more.
But I also don't want to drown you guys in content.
I need to strike a balance with it.
Like, I could probably pump out two of these vods every day.
But I don't think it's a good idea.
Like for my channel, I don't think it's a good idea to just spam the channel, you know, like that.
I try to, you know, keep it in moderation.
Too much icing is no good, guys.
It's not good for you.
Oh, no, my steak is too juicy.
My lobster is too buttery.
I've actually never had lobster.
Apparently, lobster was like a poor man's food 100 years ago.
Nowadays, it's luxury.
Isn't that weird how things change?
Yeah, never had lobster.
My favorite game, it's World of Warcraft Classic, baby.
Just imagining and thinking about that starting zone music, playing an undead or going orc in the Barrens and those areas.
Oh, man, I'm getting a tear in my eye just thinking about it.
I'm not even kidding.
Every few years, I hope Blizzard relaunches Classic just so I can play the beginning again and again and again.
I can't get enough.
I want it again and again.
I can't stop playing when it comes out, you know.
I always have to be there and be part of it.
I'm not playing WoW right now, actually.
Although, yesterday, I was actually super close.
I had my finger on the subscribe button to try out the Burning Crusade Classic.
And I... last moment, I was like, let's not do that.
Bad idea.
But I almost did it.
But I'm not playing right now.
It's funny, you mentioned... I guess I just mentioned WoW because someone asked to play it.
Never mind.
Well, you play Path of Exile 2.
It's out of early access.
Is it?
No shit.
Wait, when did that happen?
We are talking about Path of Exile, right?
Or are you talking about something else?
That is Path of Exile, no?
Path of Exile 2.
Wait, release date?
2024?
Oh, if it's out.
Oh, sorry, I misread.
Sorry, my bad.
That's on me.
Yes, actually, I want to play it.
It's one of the things I've been looking forward to.
In fact, I want to play some of those Diablo-type games.
Even Diablo, actually, I want to play.
But yeah, I heard it's in early access.
A lot of people are praising it.
It's apparently really good.
I always got a little scared of Path of Exile 1.
Never really gave it a chance.
Because I heard so many people say it's really complicated and it's managing a spreadsheet almost.
I was like, yeah, I don't know about that.
Apparently, PoE 2 is much more casual.
So that's good.
I like that, you know?
PoE 1 is peak.
Is it, though?
Be honest.
Do I need a fucking PhD in online guides to even play the game?
Can I just log in and have a good time without all that?
Because that's what I want.
I don't want external software.
I just want to play the game I buy, you know?
I don't know what it is with games nowadays.
Why do you need like a wiki and a fucking spreadsheet open to play a game?
It's stupid.
In my opinion, that's me.
It's not that hard?
Okay, maybe I'll give it a shot, then.
Could be a fun experiment, I guess.
Can you say the same for World of Warcraft?
Absolutely not.
World of Warcraft is as casual as it gets.
You don't have to do absolute anything.
You don't have to install any add-ons.
In fact, I'm a big proponent of not installing add-ons at all when you play World of Warcraft.
I think add-ons are dumb and they should be banned from the game.
You can absolutely play World of Warcraft Classic with no help from outside.
It's so good.
It's why I'm so much in love with it, actually.
I'm a real purist.
You don't even know.
When Classic relaunched like a year ago or so, they were gonna introduce the dual talent specialization in Classic and I was a big no to that.
I thought that was a horrible idea, but everyone else like, yeah, finally, you know, and it's just and I'm just like, this is how it starts.
This is how it starts.
That's me.
I'm very pure.
I did hear about the Bloodborne movie.
Apparently, Jacksepticeye is gonna produce it.
That timeline we live in.
I think it's awesome.
I'm gonna watch it.
Yeah, it's real.
Least favorite game?
That's a hard question.
Because the terrible games I don't even think about anymore.
How about least favorite game that I love?
It's one of those love-hate relationships.
I will say Elite Dangerous.
That game has so much potential and I hate it at the same time.
Because, I don't know, it's just not going anywhere, man.
It's so sad.
But I want to love it.
Would you continue Elden Ring?
I'm done with Elden Ring.
What do you mean?
I did actually consider, maybe a couple weeks ago, I had my handheld and I thought, you know what?
Should I sit on the couch and play it again right now as a Dex character?
I almost did it, but I didn't do it.
But I may do it soon.
What handheld do you have?
Just a shitty tablet.
Like an Android tablet.
But the thing is, I stream games from my PC to my tablet.
It is insane.
I don't know if you guys have ever done this.
It is actually... I don't know why nobody's talking about this.
I get one millisecond of latency.
With decoding and sending it over the network, NVNC, like there's no lag.
It feels absolutely native.
And I'm someone who's very sensitive to input lag.
Like all of those online services where you play games via the internet.
No way.
I could never do that with any game.
Not even controller games.
But when you stream it at home on local network over Wi-Fi, you don't feel any difference.
It's insane.
And you can play like something... like my computer can play...
let's say Cyberpunk, right?
That's a very demanding game.
Mac settings, path tracing, all the bells and whistles.
Stream directly to my tablet in my handheld.
It looks insane on that little screen because it's so sharp.
And it runs just as well as it does on my computer, right?
It's fucking nuts.
All you need is a decent processor in the tablet that can actually decode fast enough.
That's all you need.
Yeah, exactly.
Homemade Google Stadia.
It is... so you can use Steam Remote Play, but it does have quite a bit of latency.
I couldn't play with it.
I thought it was too much.
So I'm running with Artemis on my tablet and Apollo on my main PC.
And it's super lightning fast.
It is so much better.
Not only that, but I can also directly just control my computer if I want to.
Not that I would like to do that, but you can, you know.
Okay, guys.
It's time to play some Isaac.
I can't wait.
Let's fucking do this.
Last time was crazy!
Okay, let's see here.
Look at that.
I think we're ready to do some damage, huh?
Let's see the wind streak.
Oh, wait, I thought it was two.
Shit.
Wait, didn't I win two in a row?
Huh, I guess I didn't.
I'm pretty sure I won twice last time, though.
I maybe had a loss in between.
Okay, so we're gonna start off with a random, shall we?
I'm going in.
Wish me luck.
Roll the dice!
Brother.
I swear to god, this game is rigged.
It's so rigged.
Okay, I gotta get into gaming mode now.
Okay, I can't need to focus.
Yeah, you want to poop?
That's cool.
I almost got hit by that.
That was very close.
Actually, I need to poop before I kill you, because then I can poop again.
Not that it did much there.
Oh, no.
Not a good start.
This guy jumped right into my face.
Come here.
Nice.
Any rocks?
Doesn't look like it.
No bombs yet.
Whoa, yep, Sadaisy.
Oi, yoi, yoi.
These guys are actually kind of annoying.
Come on, let me hit you.
There we go, he's down.
Oish.
Good thing they have a little less range than I do.
Come on.
I'm doing pretty good with the dodging.
Dude,
that guy has so much HP.
Okay, that was... whoa!
Almost got hit by that flame.
Scary stuff.
Okay, we can't see our HP, but I'm pretty sure we have two and a half hearts.
That's the deal right now.
I don't want anything here.
Wait, what is this one again?
Bombs detonates all place the bombs, while hell the bombs do not detonate right.
Keep moving.
This will be a crazy warm-up though, with the blue boy.
Oh, they're so annoying.
Okay, good.
Just play patient.
No need to do anything hasty.
Get those flies.
Ah, this room.
It's actually not that bad.
For a while I struggled with this room, but I know how to do it now.
Consistently is what I mean.
Go a little bit like that.
That's how you do it.
Look at that aim.
Give me an AWK.
Put me in the middle.
Uh, no rocks.
Okay.
Oh, I should have made my poop.
I'm in trouble.
Maybe.
Wait, this guy spawns fires.
Come here.
Wow.
Man, that is tough.
Okay, there we go.
I don't want to lose HP to these flames.
That would be terrible.
Okay, good.
Okay, we got a boss.
Uh, we haven't found a treasure room.
I really want to find that first.
That could be like a game-changing item in there.
You never know.
Okay.
No bombs though.
What's that?
It's a new one!
Frankly ball.
Gotta fetch them all.
That's a Pokemon reference.
Throws a ball that will capture the first regular monster it strikes.
Throw again to release the captured enemy as a permanently friendly monster.
Cannot capture bosses or minibosses.
Oh, that's cool.
But what about my poop?
So, it's a one-time use, I guess.
Fuck, all the monsters are gone.
Ah, guess I'll keep it for next floor.
Now, okay, let's go.
Wait, uh, why is the duke all brown?
He's like beige colored now.
This is a variation of the duke.
Duke, I'm your father.
What?
Careful.
There's too many flies.
Wait, we gotta get some damage in.
Good.
Here come the flies.
Oh god.
Yeah, he's way more aggressive than normal.
I'm gonna try and kite him a little bit here.
Run around like that.
Run down.
Uh-oh.
That is actually bad.
Get him!
Nice.
Focus, focus.
Sick.
That was so clean.
Like, come on.
Beautiful.
Uh, consolation prize.
What's it gonna be?
My, uh, tears.
That's pretty good.
And we got a bomb too.
I may actually go back with that.
Was there anything worth bombing?
Let's double check for tinted rocks before we leave.
Hold on, there's actually a fly in my eye.
Okay, he's gone now.
I had to lift the eyelid to make him buzz out of there.
That was uncomfortable.
I could bomb some of this and get money, but I'm not gonna.
Nah, I'm good.
Move on.
I would say this is a solid first floor.
Except losing a bit of HP in the very beginning there.
That was a blunder.
That shouldn't have happened.
We're way behind the timer right now.
Guys, today we're gonna try and catch up to that timer.
Like, actually, full-blown speedrun.
If we get the right character, of course.
You wanna get a good character.
Something like a Seizel.
If we happen to get a Seizel, I'm gonna speedrun the shit out of it.
If not, then we're gonna take it slow.
This is the plan.
Come here.
How am I gonna get in there?
That's annoying.
Sir!
Okay, that's good.
Fantastic.
Uh, rotten tomato.
Chance to fire special tears.
The bait.
Slows enemies and draws other nearby enemies to attack them instead of Isaac.
Chance increases with luck.
All right.
I guess that's fine.
Nothing spectacular, I don't think.
Uh, wait, I'm bleeding tomato juice.
Look at that.
Or drooling, I guess.
Come at me.
Okay, good.
Very slow and calculated.
Oh god.
Focus, you dumbass.
Ooh, guys, can we turn set?
Nah, I'm not gonna do that again.
I know when to stop gambling.
I'm not gonna push my luck.
Also, I need to figure out when to use my Pokeball.
Fuck!
We are currently at one and a half hearts.
Oh yeah, I can see it too.
I was calculating because I thought I couldn't see my hearts.
Uh, let's go up here.
Oh well.
You know who I want to grab?
What?
Where did you come from?
Like, I swear that guy wasn't there.
He just appeared out of nowhere.
You know what?
What?
I, uh, okay.
I missed.
It's unfortunate.
Okay.
I thought for sure I had a full HP there.
I thought, uh, I had a full heart.
I was wrong.
Go again.
Come on.
Uh, Eden, okay.
Sounds good.
Uh, so this is, oh, three hearts in blue.
Dude, what is this character?
Teleports Isaac to another room.
Crown of Light!
Wait a minute, is that...
Glowing crown?
Insane, yes!
That's the one!
When all red hearts are full, tears become diamonds and deal double damage.
Taking damage removes the effect for the room.
That is insane.
Like, what is this character?
Hello?
Kind of want to start stepping as well.
We'll see how it goes.
Oh, I have a very slow attack speed though.
Holy!
Oh, rip my diamonds.
Dude, this attack speed is horrendous.
Oh, it's painful.
I'm a little less excited now.
Surely we can fix that with some items, right?
Let me actually try the teleport.
Uh-huh.
Should we be step...
Let's wait a bit and see if we find some hearts.
Depending on how many we find, we may be...
Uh, we're gonna step a little bit.
Wait, I need to understand this crown right now?
I thought I... Oh, God.
Oh, come on, man.
I need to see something.
Taking damage removes the effect for the room.
Got it.
And then we have...
Call me crazy, I've had this like three times.
How is it not identified at this point?
Forever alone.
Have I not had this before?
Familiar that orbits at a far distance and deals contact there.
Like...
Hmm.
That is so weird.
I'm gonna blow up this wall here.
Uh, let's do the one on the left.
I have a feeling.
It's a strong one today.
Fantastic gameplay!
Look at that, I'm rich as well.
Insanity.
Okay.
I guess I'm a mini solar system right now as well.
I could use that to my advantage.
Geez, sus.
Uh, nothing in here.
Come at me.
Okay.
Look at this here.
Oh, I don't have any bombs.
Shit.
Hmm.
I can almost buy this item.
Doubles the effects of most active items.
Oh, wait, let me teleport actually.
placebo?
No, I don't want that.
I'm not excited by these items at all.
Okay.
Remind me again exactly how this works.
It's just a random room.
I do wonder though if it can teleport me to a secret room.
If I haven't been there already.
Because there's also another teleport item that teleports me in a certain order, right?
I'm not sure if it's actually the same idea.
I think this one is true random.
The other one was fake random.
Boom!
I need
to find some attack speed here.
Uh, you know what?
Let's blow this up because this could reveal something.
Oi!
Well, there we go!
We're gonna find bombs now.
I can't move these unfortunately.
Can I...
okay.
Okay.
Uh, I guess I'm just gonna teleport.
I missed the room.
There we go.
We're gonna go get that tinted rock now.
Now to remember where it was.
I think here, yeah.
Should I play risky?
This should kill it, right?
Could also reveal a room.
Okay, nice.
All right.
Eh, I'm happy with that.
I have 16 coins.
I think I'll save for the next shop.
This is the plan.
Right!
The haunt!
This is gonna be a little tough with my tears, I think.
These guys move erratically.
But I have good damage, as long as I have the diamonds.
Oh god.
You little piece of shit.
I'm gonna solo system this man.
No, I'm gonna blow him up, of course.
One, two...
Aha!
Let's do the other side now.
One, two...
Boom!
That is amazing.
Oh, the matchbook!
That's so funny.
I already have the match.
One black heart.
Before I do, though...
Ah, we don't have any deals, unfortunately.
Ah, okay.
In that case.
Thanks.
I will go back.
Because now I have extra bombs.
And I think there was something else I wanted to bomb somewhere.
Let me think.
Oh, this is for sure a secret room here, no?
Hold on.
Let me check from this side.
Okay, when there's rocks along the wall, I am actually unsure if that is a secret room.
Let me try once.
Okay.
I think there is a rule with that.
Let me see.
Do I wanna do this?
I don't know why I suddenly had a lisp.
I'm gonna lose...
Is it half a heart every time?
I have half a heart of healing, but I'm gonna have to go through my blue heart.
Let's wait.
The next stepy room, we're gonna step.
Save it for now.
That sounds good.
And I don't want anything from the shop, so we're just gonna saunter on along.
Cheers.
Alright, Eden.
Wait, we got a shit ton of damage.
Oh, it's because we got diamonds.
Makes sense.
I'm just gonna play it super safe here.
No reason to be hasty.
Beautiful.
Yep.
Alright, let me teleport.
It is kind of exciting, though.
Every time I teleport, I get excited.
Like, it feels good in my tummy.
Come here.
Um, that's cool.
Up, up, up, up.
We're gonna be caught in the corner here.
Oh, that was close.
Oh, shit, I have no keys.
Damn, we gotta find some.
We're rich!
Thanks!
We gotta find the shop now.
I will take this later, I think.
For now, I'm gonna chill.
Where you guys going, eh?
Come back here.
Oh, you're gonna blow up now.
Nice.
Dude, I frickin' love this game.
I am just so happy when I play it.
No, I don't have a key for that, either.
Shit!
Okay, I'm actually starting to hate this game.
We gotta get some keys.
Otherwise, I'm not gonna love it.
I'm gonna hate it.
Wah!
That was almost like a one-on-one on FY pool day, there.
Only scouts.
I need, I need key.
I don't think these guys can spawn keys, though.
Wah!
Maybe it can now!
Come on!
Dah!
I'm gonna leave the matchstick.
Dude, where are the keys at?
You can't do me dirty like this.
Not when I have 28 gold in the bank.
Ready to be spent at the nearest shopping facilities.
How am I missing?
Okay, time for the fly to make an appearance.
I'm gonna wait for the orbit.
I'm gonna slingshot.
Oh my god.
Dude, this attack speed is killing me!
Close.
Uh, I can step on this, because it's not glowing.
Sir!
What a shot.
Nice.
Time to die.
Come on!
There we go.
So, any tinted rocks?
I don't think so.
I mean, we could get lucky with the teleport.
Come on.
Oh, uh, oh, I made it to the shop, I guess.
Oh, shit.
That was bad, that was bad.
Unnecessary damage taken.
Oh, wait, that's not the shop.
Oh, okay.
Ah, man, you...
Oh, we got three keys!
Wait, where did we get those keys?
Was that just now?
I don't fucking recall.
I'm not gonna question it, we're gonna use them.
Yeah!
Wait, what's this?
Red candle?
Obviously I'm taking this.
This is not an active, right?
Fuck it is!
No!
Launches directional flame attack that damages...
Dude.
Well, that's cool.
But, uh, I like this.
Yeah, let's not walk in that flame.
Let's find a backpack.
Also, I will get in here.
I will rob the bank.
Kinda wanna buy the pill.
Oh, I need to convert.
Of course.
Uh, before I forget.
Uh, let's see here.
I think I'll buy a key, actually.
We're kinda short on keys these days.
Yeah.
Fuck the pill!
Maybe I'll try a no pill run.
Oh, but it feels so good, though.
This is definitely a secret.
Watch this.
How am I so good at this game?
I don't actually understand my own powers.
Uh...
Go!
I believe.
I believe, I believe, I believe!
Shit!
Okay, now.
Yeah!
I'm rich.
Okay, let's go to the treasure room.
Now that we have a key.
Oh, there's a key here as well, actually.
Forgot that.
Oh, what is that one?
Three coins, more coins.
Yeah, sure.
Not that I need it.
How is it this game is just like, okay, now you're broke forever.
And now you're a king.
And you get to buy everything, forever.
Like, there's no middle ground.
Thanks.
Oh, shit.
That's totally cool.
Let's go!
Monstro!
There's two of them.
Oh, this is actually getting problematic.
Oh my god.
Yo, there's not a lot of room to navigate here.
Yeah, have a bomb.
He dodged out of that, that's crazy.
Did you see that?
I'm gonna wait for one of them to jump.
There, bomb.
That was beautiful!
Ho, ho, ho, MLG.
MLG.
And we're gonna convert as well in just a second here.
No devil deals.
That's cool.
Do I want to do anything else on this?
Actually, I do.
We do have some extra...
Oh, no, actually, I can't waste my blue heart.
No, no, no, I can't, I can't do it.
I can't do it.
Oh my god, that was close.
I nearly fucked it up.
Ho, ho, let's move on.
Okay.
We need a little...
Okay, so, wait a minute.
A hundred percent devil now.
And this is floor...
Three?
No, I don't remember.
Four, maybe?
I did not really keep track.
Peek your little head.
Thank you, fly.
The fly is actually totally good here.
I should use it more.
Okay, this one is a little bit...
No, it's easy.
I'm playing this as if I was BB right now.
Because that way, I mean, I will be unstoppable.
Huh?
Oh, my fly destroyed it.
Okay.
Sabotage.
Absolute sabotage.
Doi!
DVD logo moment.
Zohai yaba!
Not bad.
The converter is ready for action.
Oh, god.
He made me run into the fire.
Okay, can we stop doing that?
Habra, habra!
This room!
I'm gonna die!
Fucking hell, what a room.
I think I should have killed the small ones first.
My strategy was not sound.
Ah, you gotta be actually kidding me.
Need to focus up here.
Not this.
You gotta be kidding me.
There we go, use the fly.
There you go, you like that?
And fly for you!
Dude, the fly is incredible.
Shit, well, one and a half hearts is not a lot.
Let me tell you.
What's that?
Nice.
Okay, this is huge.
This could be good.
Oh, yeah, that's good.
That's good.
I'll be taking that.
I'll also be taking this one.
Let's see what we get.
The lovers, that is incredible.
The lovers.
And we have the chariot.
Two chariots, okay.
Copies the effect of Isaac's active item.
Hey, that's kind of cool as well.
Two of hearts, doubles, Isaac's red.
Let's use that now.
We can actually step, if we find a stepper.
Let's go with the chariot for now.
I have a lot of money.
No bombs, let's take this.
Good.
And we get a reveal map.
The world.
Okay, we just undid the huge mistakes we've been doing for the last two minutes.
That's mega.
Mega massive.
Oh, you're tempting me.
Okay, we're doing pills.
Fuck!
Why did I do pills?
I need to stop.
I need to get rid of this addiction.
It's real.
Now I don't know where the secrets are.
No!
I don't know where the fucking secret room is.
I think it was here.
Yeah, okay, good.
But there's probably another one that I now miss, right?
So, rip that.
Oh, the flag!
Oh!
Dude, okay, dude.
We cannot lose this now.
We cannot lose now.
This is incredible.
Ah!
Oh, wait.
Gotta be careful.
Stop pooping out flies.
Good.
We have a floor decoration here, too.
We can find a shovel.
Man, these guys have some HP.
I'm always surprised that they're HP pool every time.
They're chonky.
Little chonkers.
Oh, god.
Sick!
I did that pretty well.
Oh, god.
Oh, yeah, I can fly!
Haha!
Right!
I gotta get used to that.
What a great feeling, huh?
You can't reach me.
What are we gonna get?
Oh, that's the toxic one.
Toxic shock!
This is one that poisons all enemies at the start of each room, dealing damage over time.
Destroyed enemies also leave behind a small creep pool.
That is great.
Let's experiment with the secret places here, even though I don't know where they are.
Actually, I should take this up here instead.
Just because I have another barrel in the bottom right.
Come on, come on.
No, this way now, this way now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Good enough.
Ah, okay.
Nothing there.
I wonder if there's an easier way to do this.
Crap!
I tried.
This is called Optimized Gameplay.
At least an attempt at it.
Let's see, did I miss anything back here?
There were a couple of cards that I wanted to bring, I think.
Oh, shit!
Oh, yeah, they got poisoned.
Right.
Hmm, where's that room with all the cards?
I could go in here.
With the chariot.
I can exit again.
You know what, why not?
I've got extra cards.
Somewhere.
Not that way.
Here.
Now, what do I want to bring with me?
The chariot, or death, or maybe even...
Cop?
Nah.
This one could be...
Nah, it's not good, it's not good.
Let's take chariot.
Chariot is solid.
And I don't recall whether or not there was a step room here, but if there was...
I would love to go in there, because I only have red hearts and I have a bunch of healing.
Fuck it.
It's Mega Man.
So far, so good.
This has got to be one of the easiest bosses, right?
I mean, I was just standing still there.
Jesus juice!
It's good, but I would love to get some more tears.
Because I'm not shooting very fast.
This is like the main thing, you know?
Uh, okay.
I don't know what that was.
Damage... oh!
Or two red?
I mean, I have converters, so I think I'm comfortable with that.
We're going to easily find more.
That should not be a problem.
That's an easy W there.
Okay.
We're going to do that, of course.
And then we're... oh, oh!
Yeah, just... did you see that?
When you convert a black heart, you actually deal damage to the rune.
Holy shit!
That's massive!
I can use that strategically.
Also, look at this place.
This is new.
Wait, oh, they died to the poison?
Oh my god, the water is flowing down the wall in runes.
You see that?
It's spelling out...
I-D-I...
Oh, oh, okay.
Whatever.
What are these enemies?
Dude, this is so cool!
What's up, dude?
Oh yeah, I can fly, I have to remember.
Look for stuff?
Oh, they died!
I should use it...
No, actually, I think it's better to do the way I'm doing it.
Lil' Dumpy.
It's a familiar that automatically produces a butterbean fart when an enemy or a projectile comes close to hitting Isaac.
After triggering this effect, Lil' Dumpy flies off, becoming inactive, and must be walked over to reactivate.
I like it!
It's not a Lil' Gertie, but it'll have to do.
Does it see mine?
Sick.
Dude, this game is so cool, there's so much stuff!
The moon!
The moon is great!
I love the moon.
More bombs?
What was that card over here?
That was the chariot, right?
Take me!
Sick.
Oh, okay.
Oh my goodness.
A door has opened?
We need to find it.
Wait, is that it in here?
Oh, I see you.
I see you.
Nice.
I had to do it, guys, in case I accidentally lost some HP, you know, I can't take that chance.
Okay.
Although, you know, optimally, you would use it in a room, but whatever.
Man, the toxic thing is fantastic.
We can definitely donate to this man.
But I think we should wait until we find a shop, just in case.
You don't know what we're gonna find in there, right?
Looks like those mines are indeed immune to poison.
These guys are not immune to poison.
Which I enjoy very much.
Massive enjoyer of that fact.
Man, I got some good damage right now.
Like, I am fucking killing it right now.
And this place looks super awesome.
Love the visual effect.
Go.
Okay,
so what do we got?
What a shit shop.
Are you messing with me?
Hamnesia, right.
I mean, I guess we'll get this.
Two of clubs.
That's bombs, right?
Yeah.
I like.
In fact, I'm gonna run around with this for a while.
I'll come back to get the...
I'll come back for the converter.
Uh, crossing fingers.
Okay, let's go here.
Oh, look at this fatty.
He's puking.
He's dead.
We even got the poop, so we could get items here.
Fantastic.
Now, the boss is beckoning.
But I say no to that.
I'm not ready for that.
I really want to go step.
Every time I want to step, there's no step, you know?
It do be like that, though.
Doubles the keys.
I mean, sure.
May as well.
Okay, you know what?
I'll give you a bunch of money, then.
If the shop is so bad.
You better give me something good, though.
Oh!
Okay, guys.
We're getting into a full-blown addiction now.
Yeah!
Back for the converter!
We're gonna convert.
Lovely.
We're gonna run with that for a bit until we can convert the other one.
There's a big triangle room up here that I want to explore.
The music here is so good!
Oh!
The guitar coming in!
The layering!
I love layers.
As something Watch Dogs did, the first Watch Dogs game, to this day, few games have surpassed it in terms of, like, dynamic music.
The way they layer tracks on top of each other in that game, depending on what's going on in the scene, is fucking phenomenal.
More games should do it.
It is such...
a good execution.
What was this card?
Actually, wait a sec.
I can use that to get in here, without losing my blue heart so I can still convert later on.
Am I optimizing a what right now?
Holy shit!
Pills!
Yes!
We needed that!
You know what?
We had too much range.
It's fine.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Oh, yeah.
Now, what card am I going to bring, though?
Oh, we should be looking for secrets.
I have ten bombs.
There's definitely one here.
Ah, but wait, wait.
Look, there's a mushroom right there, where the door would be.
So, I'm actually going to go out on a limb and say there's no secret room there.
Yeah.
What about here?
There's water?
Uh...
Maybe here.
Let's check from the other room here.
Aha!
Look at this!
So, that can't be, because the secret rooms need to have walls open on all sides, right?
At least, I think so.
Where could it be?
Let's look down here.
Let's actually try and understand this.
Usually, they like to tuck them in between other rooms, right?
So, stuff like this room, but there's water here, so I'm going to say no.
Maybe here.
Shit, okay, then maybe down here.
Okay.
Could be between the treasure room and the room above it.
Let's just kill the boss.
We have a blue heart right now, so I would love to keep that.
We'll see how it goes, though.
Holy damage.
Beautiful.
Convert!
The conversion has happened.
We get that range back.
Love it.
Bigger tier size.
Okay, I'm actually going to go back now.
I have eight bombs.
I can definitely still attempt some more secret room explosions.
Honestly, it could also be there.
Let's see here.
I think it's in between the treasure room and the room above that.
Ah, but look at this here.
Fuck!
Maybe here.
I'm losing my mind.
Okay, all the way at the end over here.
That's obvious, right?
It's got to be right here.
No, it can't be.
Ah!
I give up.
Let's leave.
Then again, wait a minute.
Here?
Did I check that already?
Fuck, I think I may have.
Okay, let's not waste any more bombs.
We're done here.
We're getting out.
Okay, let's just play it safe.
Ah, actually?
Yeah, yeah.
Go, go.
I thought I left behind a card or something.
Cheers.
This room is... I mean, this run is just textbook, uh...
Fantastic.
Like, if you look up fantastic in the dictionary, you will see this run appear.
A fork.
A chance to heal half a red heart each time you clear a room.
Uh, I don't need that.
I would rather have items from poops.
Maybe I'll come back for it later if, you know, shit hits the fan.
Oh, don't you dare.
Sir.
Oh, nice poop!
That poop saved me a little bit there.
Oh my god.
Insanity.
Uh, AAA battery.
Restores the final charge of a...
Hey, that... I don't need that, actually.
I feel like the converter needs to have, like, ten charges and not three.
It's... it's fucking strong, man.
Like, three charges for that shit?
That's crazy.
Oh, wait, I can't take damage from the creep.
I have to keep that in mind.
Now, what do we have here?
So, this one is simply... weird to me.
So, what runes do we know of?
We know of the rune that digs a hole.
We know of the rune that reveals the map.
And those are the two I know about.
So, if I use this now, will I get any of those effects?
Let me stand over a floor decoration, at least, when I do.
Maybe that's bone.
Okay, we gained half a blue heart.
Interesting.
Strength, I'll take it.
And what is this up here?
Okay.
Nice.
I need a shop.
What is that?
Oh, whoa!
Wait.
I actually don't know if this is better than my converter.
I mean, I'll use it once.
Wait, wait.
I can use it once, then switch back to the converter at the end of the run.
Or at the end of the floor.
I will actually prefer to keep my converter for the most part.
It's definitely amazing.
Good item.
See, here's an X on the floor.
I need shot speed.
That's what I need.
Holy crap, my projectiles are slow.
What?
What on earth is this?
Holy!
I've never seen this.
That's freaking awesome.
We're going to be here a while.
Okay.
Guys, are we going to find a ten coin in here?
In one of these?
I say yes.
Watch.
One of these is going to have a ten coin.
I'm tempted to blow it up.
Maybe they can't actually spawn a ten coin.
See, I don't know that.
Maybe that's not a thing that can happen.
Shit.
We got close to ten coins.
In any case.
All in all.
Another one of those.
Oh, we're going to step.
We're totally stepping.
But not yet.
Not quite yet.
This is a secret room.
One hundred percent though.
Okay.
My statistics are off here apparently.
I need to revise those estimates.
Wait, that was half a blue heart.
Oh, okay.
I was ready to convert that shit.
Uh, what's this?
The D6.
This is the one I unlocked.
Re-roll all pedestal items in the room with a different item from the room.
Ooh!
Yo!
Wait, hold up now.
Hmm.
I may actually keep that.
That sounds really fucking strong.
But...
Not yet.
Soon.
I can fly, so of course I'm good.
Uh...
No!
Ew!
Yes!
Convert!
Yeah!
That's fine, that's okay.
I almost just did it automatically.
Do not range down me.
Oh god.
That's the boss.
Very nice.
We got blue flames in here, you know what that means.
Conversion!
Oh!
The shop!
No!
I thought it was a real shop.
How sad is that?
Actually, you know what?
I could take more damage here and get more money if I wanted.
But I'm not...
Oh, wait, that's gonna work with the...
With the step, isn't it?
I'm totally losing too much HP here for no reason.
I need to...
Dude, this guy!
Hello?
Brother!
Stop!
I'm too careless.
Well, I'm definitely rich now.
This has reduced my effectiveness of step.
Just a tad bit.
But it's okay.
I will step in this life for the next.
Mark my words.
I got some worms in here.
Whoa.
So much money.
Too much money.
Okay, let's go.
Let's do a bit of stepping.
I feel blessed.
Lost the demon mode?
Gained angel!
Ha!
I'll be back.
I shall be back.
Whoa!
Nice!
We love that.
Oh, we don't love that.
We do actually love that.
Ha ha!
Now, at this point, I'm actually gonna stop converting.
Because the last two hearts, I think I wanna turn into black hearts.
This is the strategy.
This is the thing I wanna change this time around.
We have done enough converting.
The time of conversion is over.
Oh, thanks, buddy.
I need to find a couple more hearts so I can keep stepping.
Dude, come on.
Wow, he got hit by the spikes as well.
I didn't realize enemies could take damage from that.
Isn't that kinda neat?
Oh, goodness.
Gracious.
Let's look for some secrets.
Oh, that's huge.
Give me healing.
I need a lot of healing here.
Is it just me, or is this floor really big?
Like, this is a big-ass floor.
Bigger than usual.
Oh, this guy's different.
He has Isaac on his back head.
Any healing is very appreciated right now.
Oh, this is a champion man!
I think?
Wait.
Wait, what did I just do?
I killed him, then a skull came up?
I must have done something.
Um...
I don't know what just happened.
Oh, healing, there we go.
Ah, I stepped into that like an idiot.
Ah, you gotta be shitting me, man.
Holy shit, this floor.
Ah, I can stay in the center.
Come at me, then.
Um...
Wait, there's a...
Wait, there's two treasure ropes?
Something's happening with this floor.
It's like, things are off.
Why does that happen?
Nice!
Forgot I had those.
Let me actually... Hold on a minute.
What's happening here?
Let me see this again.
Right, we had that one.
Uh, we're gonna do that at the end.
And then we obviously gotta take the dice as well.
Uh, before we do the boss.
Oh, I actually think...
Uh, not here.
So did we find any secrets yet?
No, we didn't.
Let's see if there's anything in here.
I'm gonna bomb this.
Crap.
What about here?
Twelve bombs left.
I can still have some fun.
Maybe in here.
Uh, I already...
No, wait, I already tried that one, didn't I?
That would be the one here.
Yeah, I tried that one already.
I need to see...
So the other treasure room...
I think that's the one where the dice was.
The D6.
Did I try bombing this?
I'm not 100%.
Okay, yeah, this is the one.
Let me grab that.
This way.
Ooh, that has a lot of charges on it.
That is a...
Big one.
Okay, right here, dude.
It's perfect.
No!
Okay, well, I guess finding secrets in a map as big as this one is gonna be difficult.
Uh, here we go!
Wish me luck.
Oh, god.
We're gonna nail this with not taking any damage.
He's good at dodging somehow.
Even though he's not.
Yeah, the bombs!
Backfired, didn't it?
Beautiful.
Okay, so watch.
I should be able to use this dice now, right?
And have two of them, or what?
Oh, no, wait, that re-rolls it, right.
Oh, do I want to re-roll, though?
This is pretty good.
Oh, that's pretty good.
Like, one tier?
I need tiers.
I need shot speed.
I need both of these.
Hell yeah.
Another boss!
Oh, it's mom.
Huh?
I thought that was next level.
Fine, we can do that now.
We can tassel!
Oh, goodness.
Gracious.
Where are you?
Okay, you're over there.
Oh, man, you're fast.
We got it.
Stay on the move.
There we go.
Oh, she's aggressive.
I mean, we can keep doing that.
That's cool.
That's for you.
Did I just bomb myself?
Okay, this one's gonna be perfect.
What?
I'm just gonna stop and try and bomb her.
Yeah, what's up with mom here?
This is super easy.
Mom?
What are you doing, mom?
I guess if you have shitty move speed here, this could be difficult.
Ah, should have kept moving in one direction there.
Okay.
Oh, wait, this is the new one!
The Polaroid, fate chosen.
Bring him the photo?
Taking damage with half or less red hearts will trigger an invincibility bubble for five...
Wait, taking damage with half or less red hearts?
How can you have less than a half red heart?
Oh, I guess if you have blue hearts.
Okay, allows access to higher stages?
Whoa, can be used to open a strange door!
Okay.
What?
Dude!
I have the key!
I have the golden key!
I think this is the combo!
I'm pulling it out of my ass, but I have a feeling about it.
A door opens, right?
When I get the golden key.
And now I have access to a...
What did it say?
Higher stage?
Exciting.
Kind of want to go step, but also don't, you know what I mean?
Yeah, okay, go.
I'm excited.
This is very exciting.
Cheers to that.
You're not going to get me.
Dude, my shot speed is so much better now because of that item we just got.
That is so good.
I finally feel like I can do something here.
Oh, goodness.
Very nice.
Feels incredible now.
Okay.
Let's go here.
Thanks, buddy.
Super wrath!
Okay.
Wait, the bombs are following me because it's the follower bombs.
Are you going to come this way or...
Oh, this guy's annoying.
At least he takes damage from his own bombs.
That makes me happy.
Yeah, dumbass.
What's that one?
Mr. Mega.
Wait, we've had this one.
Oh, no, wait, this is a different one.
Plus five bombs, bombs gain a bigger blast radius and deal more damage.
Oh, okay.
I thought it was the active that blew up the entire room, you know?
Okay.
Yeah, this way.
I need to find some healing here.
This is actually a little bit dangerous.
I got four hearts.
That is not a lot.
Not enough to make me feel safe.
The man, that fart just saved me.
Fishtail.
When blue flies are spawned, double the amount.
No.
Oh, massive healing from poops.
Actually insane.
More healing.
Dude, I'm blessed right now.
I technically am.
I do feel blessed, right?
Let's trigger him that way so we can shoot here.
Uh,
wait a minute.
Is that an axe?
Oh, okay.
I thought I saw a fucking tinted rock.
Like, call me crazy.
Okay, down.
And this way.
Oh, god!
Okay, nice.
Yo!
Threading the needle!
Did you see that?
Right between.
Okay, this is a secret room.
I meant that one.
Yeah.
I got it inverted, you know?
Oh, my god.
Lots of items.
Double Isaac's coins.
Wait, we have 99 coins?
I didn't even realize.
What the fuck?
We're rich?
Holy!
I mean, uh, hmm.
Sure.
What am I going to spend it on?
Can we get money equals power now?
That would be great, wouldn't it?
Whoopsie daisy.
Come on.
I see you there.
More bombs.
Oh, no.
I gotta play safe.
Let me see here.
We do some damage, and then we go hide again.
Actually, uh, what I could do...
This is a weird one.
Shoot and hope for the best.
Spray and pray.
Okay, that works.
Dude, look at these.
Doesn't that look like an X right there?
I'm fucking seeing things all over the place.
Wait, there's a new boss!
School X!
What's up, buddy?
Let's see what you can do.
Oh, he has a weird tail.
With a sunflower on it.
That's pretty.
You're so pretty.
Oh!
Okay, then.
Oh, wait, he only takes damage on the tail.
That's what's happening.
Oi, oi.
I have an idea.
Watch this.
I'm gonna wait for him to charge me.
That's amazing.
Decreases Isaac's... Yeah, of course, we do that one.
And...
Friends till the end.
I like it.
Let's see what we got here.
Three options!
Dark Matter.
More damage.
Chain increases with luck.
Fear Effect.
And then we have...
The Book of Sin spawns a random pickup.
Estabs Isaac at the start of each floor, depleting as many red hearts as you can with it.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That sounds not good.
Except, let me see.
Estab grants bonus damage and speed for the rest of the floor.
The more health I can fry it, the more...
I mean, if I suddenly have like a million...
Oh, wait a minute.
No.
Oh, wait, I can use this?!
Copies hit!
The mark.
Copies paw.
Ooh.
Uh...
Actually...
Wait, remove...
I think I'm actually gonna take this and this.
Yeah?
I'm gonna do this.
Use it.
Take this.
Black heart.
That is a healthy balance of red, blue, and black.
RBB.
I could also take that one.
Nah, I don't want that.
I don't want that.
Dude, the D6 is... fucking crazy.
I'm just now realizing the possibilities with this thing.
Holy...
We haven't even found a treasure room.
We gotta keep looking.
Wait.
That smells like a secret room, doesn't it?
In here...
Oh, no, never mind, it's not.
Okay.
Not too shit.
I love flying.
I love being able to fly.
I'm gonna hide inside of here.
What are you gonna do about it?
What about this guy?
Hello?
Oh, there you are.
Nice.
Not the evil poop.
Okay, I'm gonna blow all these up.
Look at all the bridges I made.
It's kinda funny.
Okay, I blow these up as well.
I'm nearing the end.
Actually, I'm not, because there's more, right?
This is not the final area.
Hagalas!
Okay, fucking use it here.
All the rocks are gone.
Nothing in them.
I don't wanna walk in there with a black heart.
That is...
not great.
I mean, I'm gonna lose half a black heart, actually.
I think we can do it.
Ah, shit!
Okay.
Fuck.
I need to remember that on the red floors, you take a full heart of damage.
You want bombs?
I should've met you earlier, man, before I wasted them all.
Okay, I'm not gonna give you all my bombs.
One more.
Okay, fuck you.
Oh!
I thought that was a thing.
Man, I'm kinda running low on bombs.
Getting a lot of keys.
Dude, we can just... we can just use the D6 again when the opportunity comes.
This is crazy.
Moving on.
Every time I leave a floor, I get this feeling.
The same feeling that I get when I leave my house.
When I'm like halfway to my destination, I go, oh shit, did I...
Did I remember to turn off the stove?
Did I lock the door?
Oh shit, did I feed Jackie?
You know what I mean?
But with like, oh, did I grab the card I left behind, or active, or whatever the fuck.
Insert, whatever, you know?
I get that feeling every time.
It's horrible.
Would you look at this arcade with all this money?
Are you ready?
Look at this one!
What the...
Dude, we can potentially step here.
No, actually I like that more.
Uh, wait, wait, wait.
I'm gonna come back here.
Wait, wait.
I wonder if this works on this.
Is this technically a pedestal?
Reroll's all pedestal items in the room.
I'm gonna try it for science.
Big... bad fly?
Familia that bounces around the room and explodes and...
You can actually do that.
I'm glad I just tested that.
We're gonna find a step room.
We're gonna do some stepping today.
That was also a death, wasn't it?
Yeah.
I never use it.
Use it now.
Uh, walking in there...
It's gonna consume a full heart, don't be fooled.
Brother, I don't need more money.
Stop!
Enough is enough!
I cannot believe that just happened.
Thanks for that fart.
Come on, please let me step somewhere.
I need to step, I need to step.
I lost both my blue hearts.
Wait, I just realized.
If I didn't like the item that I rerolled just now, I could probably just come back when I have new charges and do it again.
Dude, how crazy is that?
Like, I didn't have to take the rerolled item.
Oh my god.
It's just, I don't like this familiar I just have.
I feel like it's kind of shit.
I wish I had gotten something else.
This way first.
Very good.
Load that up.
Damn.
Come on, give me a step room.
I need to step up.
I have so much potential for healing on this floor.
Wait, now I'm shooting diamonds?
That's been a while.
Well, how come that suddenly works again?
I feel like I haven't seen that in ages.
Am I losing my mind?
Like, I haven't been shooting diamonds since floor two.
Like, it was all red tears.
I guess the visual effect just changed a bit.
Nah, I'm gonna wait with the gambling until we find a step room.
I'm gonna blow this up.
Even the screen shakes.
The bomb is so powerful.
The Empress is actually pretty good.
Ooh.
Yes.
I'm actually gonna gamble on an angel room.
That's right.
Imagine going into an angel room and using the D6, baby.
Can you imagine that?
That sounds crazy.
Now, this room was closed, right?
No.
Yeah.
We're not done clearing the bottom.
This way.
Here.
Okay, here we go.
No problem.
So that's the boss.
Surely here.
Are you kidding me?
Where is this secret...
That was my last bomb!
I didn't realize I was this low on bombs.
Oh, shit.
Okay, now we can go up.
Wild.
Okay, we're gonna go in here now.
We can keep healing.
Oh, man.
How much you wanna bet the other one is a bomb?
Yeah, it's always both bombs, isn't it?
And we're gonna heal up.
Ah, I know why.
It's because I was not full HP.
That's why I had red tears for so long.
Makes sense.
Okay, come on.
We're gonna bounce between these two.
There we go.
Nice!
And now we have diamonds again.
Unfortunately, no step room.
Like, it's every time I finally can step, I don't get the, you know, opportunity to step.
It's triggering.
But it's time to beat the boss, and then use the D6 on whatever comes out, hopefully.
Here we go!
It lives!
Nice.
Alright, let's get to it.
Wait, am I not hitting him up there?
Oh, there we go, okay.
We can't, okay, we cannot hit him when, uh...
When he's, like, up there.
He needs to be in the center.
Not bad, not bad, solid, solid.
Love it.
Wait, no item?
No item?
What the fuck is this scam?
Hello?
Where's my item?
Isn't there usually an item?
Maybe not, maybe the, the light from above is the item, you know?
This is your, this is your reward.
You get to ascend.
This guy needs to get out of here.
I mean, this is, this, this is gonna be easy.
Wait, I lost?
No, never mind.
Yeah, this is just gonna be a walk in the park, I think.
I shouldn't speak so soon.
I need to stop this talking shit.
Don't sell the skin before the bear is shot, you dumbass.
Um, let me see here.
We also only have one bomb, which is kind of sad.
It does make me sad.
The stars.
Uh, yeah, sure.
Take me to either.
Whatever.
Oh, wait, what?
Who the hell are you?
And what are you doing in here?
That's beautiful.
Nice.
A little more healing and we have the king status come back to us.
What?
Oh, was there a fly in there?
Maybe.
I think that was a fly in there.
I thought it was just straight up empty.
Hey asshole, come here.
Oh, that's cool.
That's cute.
Oh, you're gonna make a minefield here, aren't you?
Yo.
Bad feeling.
Okay, that's actually pretty good.
Dude, this music is always so hype when I get here.
Blue heart, baby, come on.
No, wow.
Flat penny.
I don't need more coins.
Get that through your head.
The game really wants me to spend all my coins.
And I would, if I could.
I'm gonna find a beggar and give him so much money, I'm gonna stuff them or shove them down his throat until he pukes.
And he's gonna love it.
Blow it up.
Wow.
I am just not doing well with my secret guesstimates today.
Oh, this guy's tough.
Wait, what?
How did he explode?
Okay.
Man, I have a feeling though.
Unreal.
Okay, this is a big bomb, right?
So it's good to shoot the spool.
Okay.
Damn, no blue hearts for me.
Rough.
I'm not gonna go in there.
It's kind of a small floor.
Oh, right, right, right, right.
Are we even gonna get an opportunity to use this d6 again?
Ooh, look at this.
The Bible!
I kind of want to try that on Isaac.
Actually, I'm gonna take both, of course, just to get the stats.
Do we have, no, we don't have three out of three then.
Oh, that's too bad.
Yeah, fuck the d6, it's not gonna be useful anymore.
Friendship ended with d6.
Bible is my new best friend.
Okay, I can't destroy those.
Oh, give me that.
Nice.
Okay, maybe this floor is bigger than I thought.
That's what she said.
Ah, you little bastard!
Okay, it is kind of small.
You ready?
Here we go!
This is gonna be so easy.
Wait, why can't I enter?
Oh!
There we go.
Okay, here we go.
Let's go, baby!
We're gonna Empress, we're gonna Bible, we're gonna fucking Rival and Bible and Hyrule.
Yeah, in the name of the gods!
Up above.
I'm gonna fuck you up, son.
I'm sad I lost my diamond status, though.
Like, that legitimately makes me sad.
What the...
Whoa!
Calm down!
You know what?
You want bombs?
I got bombs for you.
Actually, I should be bombing him.
Bombing is good.
Hey, you like bombs?
That's for you.
Shit!
Bombs for you?
I pushed the bomb into him with my projectiles.
That was hella dope.
Bomb for you?
Oh, no!
Wait,
is he healing?
How are you healing?
Maybe he heals when he damages me.
Get him out of here.
Yeah!
Nice.
Okay!
There we go, baby!
Let's see what we get.
A
black card has appeared in the basement!
Wait, what?
Quince?
Okay, calm down!
Don't panic!
What's happening?
The first five enemies killed in each room will spawn a random friendly baby familiar.
Familiar spawned by this effect are stationary and last only for the current room.
Okay.
Thanks.
I wonder if I can use... Oh, I don't have a D6 anymore.
Sci-fly is good!
That takes us to three out of three on Beals above!
Forgot what that does, but...
Let's see.
Does that affect my...
something?
I'm not sure.
What is that?
An arrow?
Cupid's arrow!
Piercing shots!
Piercing tears!
Rainbow baby!
Familiar that fires tears with many randomized effects, okay?
Where am I right now?
I'm scared!
I have no HP!
This is gonna be a short affair, isn't it?
Oh, god.
Son!
Stop it!
What's that?
What?
Is that an enemy?
What's happening?
Oh, it's mine!
It's mine!
Okay.
Oh, my god.
Dude, we're gonna die here.
Like... Yeah!
Oh, okay!
What the f- How come we went down?
I guess it's just I unlocked something.
That's cool, though!
Pretty cool!
Uh, wait a minute.
Why can't I see...
Okay, the photo.
I wonder why it looks like the top right and the bottom left are still darkened.
I think I need to go back down to, uh...
And do something there.
That's my guess right now.
Uh, let's do a random!
What's it gonna be?
Not... not...
Okay.
Eve?
Eve.
Wait, what is Eve?
Is that the whore?
I think it's the whore.
This is the one that turns, uh... fuck wild...
when she, uh... gets slapped.
Oh, fuck!
Okay, we made it.
Gimme that.
Oh, bro!
What was that?
What a dodging!
It's out of control!
You've never seen dodging like that.
Advanced strategies... are being employed here.
Come on, then.
What?
No way.
Okay.
Wafer!
Nice!
That's a huge item!
That is a huge item.
Uh, actually, I gotta go this way.
Sweet!
Well, I got no money, but let's just go window shopping.
Hmm... Sharp key... I don't... I'm not excited by these shop items.
I feel like most shop items are... not exciting!
It's very rare that I get excited by shop items.
Jera!
So wait, when I duplicate, it means it's free, right?
Maybe that was a mistake?
It was a mistake.
Two of hearts, though.
Uh, I think that's the one that spawns hearts.
It doesn't duplicate my hearts, right?
Yeah, my shots feel terrible now.
That was not a great development.
Slot machine?
Uh...
Okay, this is the one that doubles then.
May as well use it.
What a short floor this was!
Uh, Giminy!
Okay, you're tired now?
That's fine.
This is gonna take a while.
Okay, now he's gonna go crazy.
Cuz I killed his dad.
Your daddy's on fire.
I have that clip in my head.
Come on.
Is it just me, or is my damage like insanely underwhelming?
In this first boss?
Like, compared to usual, this is weird, isn't it?
Taking forever.
Either that, or this guy has abnormally large amounts of HP.
There we go.
That's mom's pearls.
Love it.
That's good.
Moving on.
Okay.
I have a coin, I mean a key, that's fantastic.
Oh no, we don't know what we're gonna get.
A giant cell?
Taking damage spawns in mini familiar.
Last until destroyed from taking enough damage.
I don't like that.
Huge not fan of that.
Oh god.
Dude, this room is fucking nuts.
Oh my god.
What's that?
Yeah, why not?
Nah, wait, with treasure room, we already did.
Maybe I'll...
I'll blow this up.
Amazing.
Question mark on that.
You know what, we're gonna blow up some mushrooms as well, so why not?
The high priestess.
That's pretty good.
I'm gonna save that heart.
I really shouldn't have eaten that pill.
I really regret eating that pill.
Nice.
Good prediction there.
Love a bomb.
I'll be back.
Oh man, all these places are so attractive to blowing up, you know.
Love to blow them all up.
Whoa.
Oi.
Dude, my damage is 2.6.
That's freaking terrible.
Alright, that's something.
Not a lot, but it's something.
I'm gonna go ahead and do that.
Okay, that's one side.
Yeah.
Come this way.
That was a bit risky there.
Oh!
Fuck, that was close.
It flashed before my eyes.
Release the spiders.
We also got a tinted rock here.
There's three bombs.
What, they can walk through that hole?
Fucking bamboozled I was.
I thought they had no exit.
Shit.
Well, okay.
This one is seven.
I'm so curious.
We gotta take it.
I'll be back with money.
We have become a whore now, though, so we're gonna deal way more damage.
But maybe the thing I want to do here is to stay at 1 HP, like, forever.
You know?
But I really don't want to do that, actually.
So, I don't know.
It's kind of a, you know...
Let me take that.
The booster pack.
Teleport to the devil or angel room.
Why not?
Yeah, see, now we have a problem.
Because I wasn't thinking.
This will kill me, right?
So, I'm not gonna do that.
Let me see here.
Grants fly.
Oh, wait, it's only for one room, though.
Double Isaac's keys.
I mean...
Why not?
Give me the keys.
And then we have this guy, become invincible.
I do have some healing, actually.
And a bomb, so let's bomb this now.
Hey, okay.
Oh, wait a sec.
Eh, we stay whore.
When we have a blue heart now.
So, it's only like the red hearts that counts, kind of.
You know what I mean.
You're not gonna laser me.
Trust me, I was born with the laser.
I was molded by it.
Okay.
Hey, love.
No, wait, we're still a whore.
Unless we're not when we leave.
Aha!
I see.
So, what you want to do is to get in with one HP, one red HP before the very last boss of the game.
And then somehow heal it all up in that room, because the effect stays in the room.
That is the pro amazing play you can make.
Okay, so we have healing now.
Why did I want healing anyway?
Just for the boss, right?
That was the point.
I think so, yeah.
There's also some cards I want to grab before I leave.
Sadooka flies.
These big flies are super duper annoying.
Ah, get away from me.
Actually, maybe the trick is to stay at range, because if I don't get close to him, he's not gonna sick them on me, right?
Let me try this.
Okay, he pushed them into me by pooping a little bit.
A little bit of poop came out.
Okay.
The question is, though, will I have access to the devil room now that I left it?
I will not.
But you know what?
I'm actually happy about that.
I couldn't see what it was anyway.
Hey, lovely.
Dude, it's going fantastic.
Now we just need some HP.
Otherwise, this is gonna go straight down the shitter.
I forgot to grab a card.
I didn't lock the door before I left home.
I left the STOVE ON!
D 'oh!
Spoda!
Come on, little fly!
Help me!
I mean, bird.
Birdy man.
Peter Folk.
That's Columbo.
Come on.
Nice.
Bro, we need some damage.
We need to become a whore.
Oh, you appeared out of nowhere.
Dude, this area is so cool looking.
Love the look.
Reminds me of the flush item.
Just a bit.
Good.
Get some healing out of it.
This is gonna be rough.
Shit.
What is that?
Question mark.
Beautiful music.
Run!
Whoa.
Sometimes, when I look at my character, I think my... my tier button doesn't work.
Because I shoot so slow.
It feels like I'm not doing anything, you know?
Oh, man.
Okay, I can definitely get in there, if I had a bomb.
Yeah.
Oh, it's a step.
Oh, why is it stepping now?
I didn't call a step, did I?
Come on.
Did you have a key, though?
That's something.
Monster manual.
I'm not intrigued.
I am very underwhelmed.
But I shall... ooh.
Wait, what the...
What is that effect?
Oh, that's cool.
I thought it was the little brimstone guy.
Sick.
Maybe this is how I'm going to do damage now.
Because I don't really have any other way to do it.
Okay, let me charge up here.
Let's try this.
Okay!
Wow, you can throw far.
Oh, god.
It's not that much damage, but it's... it's respectable.
They just keep shooting, huh?
I got one coin.
It's funny, isn't it?
Like, the one time where I need a lot of money...
and that's when they give me the fucking re-roll option as well.
It's crazy.
I love that effect on it.
It's actually so well done.
Like, graphically and...
sound-wise and all that.
It's beautiful.
The way that works.
Satisfying as hell.
Oh.
And my damage is good now, because of that.
It's what I needed.
I'm not gonna use my bomb on that.
Should I use my bomb here?
There was another place I wanted to use the bomb.
But this is fine.
Less tears.
No, thanks.
Oh, it's gonna blow up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Good, good, good.
Question mark?
Hey!
Wait, if I do it again...
Can I have two?
No way!
Sick!
Did that work?
Oh, I got the fly, I think.
I'm not entirely sure what I just got.
Let's just go.
I feel good about this.
Oh, God.
He messed up.
Charging me there.
Nice.
That's huge.
I wanna clear the rest here.
This is going pretty well.
But there is something that I don't think I'm fully utilizing with this character.
So obviously you wanna stay at 1 HP for the damage.
But you don't really wanna stay at 1 HP because then you're gonna die.
So I'm not sure how to strike that balance yet.
I guess finding a bunch of blue hearts is the strategy perhaps, or black hearts, you know?
I'm actually gonna do this.
Yep.
Okay!
Totally worth.
We have 9 coins now.
We could potentially go back to the shop as well.
Oh, I can't fight.
Too bad.
I left behind a card, it seems.
Oh, I can't get in there.
Okay.
Man, I really wanna stab.
Hey!
That's 15 coins.
Let's go to the shop.
Even though I wasn't thrilled with the selection.
We charge 1 bar of Isaac's active item each time he takes damage.
If I re-roll, I'm gonna get 14 coins.
I'm probably gonna have around 12 coins when I finally get a re-roll, so I don't think it's worth it.
I will save this for the next floor.
This is the plan.
Save it for the next floor and then hopefully get something good.
Flooded caves too!
Alright!
Oh my god, look at all this!
Answers?
Yes.
Jira duplicates all...
So let's see what this one does now.
Pay attention to HP.
Okay, we have 3 and a half stats.
I think we got a red fly.
Yeah, that's what that was.
We also have a Hordensack that is vibrating on our chest.
I will take a Jira.
Man, I got so used to having that little familiar.
Now I'm back to being a nobody.
Oh, that is actually so sad.
I've tasted sweetness and then it was taken from me.
Like this damage is atrocious.
It is so bad.
I do wonder if the stains they leave on the floor here...
The creep, if that is nullified by the water.
Because it doesn't seem to flash.
Oh, I don't have a bomb.
Shiese.
Why is this guy not minding me paying any attention to me?
That's weird.
Soon we can have a monster with us.
That's gonna be nice.
Oh, that hit me.
Wow.
The bird is helping a lot.
Let's go to the treasure room.
Holy shit!
Nice.
Oh, that was my last bomb.
I don't know why I did that.
Panic, I guess.
Okay, what do we get?
Okay.
That's fine, I guess.
Oh, I didn't mean to go that way.
That was a mistake.
Nice.
We got the bomb back.
The Jittery guys?
No.
Gain battery, though, for taking damage.
Nice.
What's that on the floor?
Oh, okay.
Minecrafter.
Spawns a pushable TNT barrel.
Using the item again detonates the barrel.
I'll use it here.
No, let's use it in here.
Maybe over here, actually.
Yeah, right here.
So let me see how this works again.
I need to be absolutely sure.
Spawns it.
Using the item again detonates.
Okay.
Damn.
The Monster Manual is my only source of damage right now.
It's sad as hell.
Okay, we can go that way.
Oh my god!
Fuck, I'm an idiot.
The fucking map is revealed.
Shit.
Bring it back.
We know where the secrets are.
That is hilarious.
Oh god.
Look at all my familiars.
Okay, so here it is.
Leave it there.
Nice.
You want blood?
Nah.
You ain't getting that from me.
Not yet, at least.
Maybe soon.
Also, we gotta blow up the other question mark.
This music is such a vibe.
Whoa.
Careful, careful.
Like artillery!
Wow.
Okay, that's big.
So we can blow up from this side.
Nice!
Okay, more coins.
I can dig it.
I should have gone back for the monster manual first.
Fuck off.
Let's go grab it.
I could blow up something.
Maybe we should get a chest somewhere.
I forgot where I needed to blow things up.
Maybe in here.
Do we have any sus rocks?
Doesn't look like it.
Let's get to that shop up there.
I see you up there.
Beckoning me.
Calling my name.
Yes, I'm coming.
Let's beeline it.
Yeah, that is rough.
Focus.
Thank you, bird.
That's a good one!
We like that one.
Dude, I have a frickin' army right now.
I need to see exactly what it is that spawns all these little babies.
I'm not 100% sure.
Let me see, which one was that?
This one.
The giant cell.
Oh, they're hiding.
Okay, I can do this.
Wish me luck.
What?
Oh, shit.
Wait, what?
I'm not touching it!
Oh, wait, they go back up, of course.
I'm an idiot.
Fuck, that wasn't...
We take the steam sail.
We take it, and then we take it.
I wish I could have used this hourglass before.
Wait a minute.
Reminds time.
I think I need the monster manual, though.
Like, it is actually a must.
Well, that was a pitiful performance just now.
Not my best moment, let's just say that.
Dude, this...
How did I not take damage from that?
Masterful.
I need just a little bit more mana so I can get another familiar.
Or maybe it's okay.
Dude, I should have used Jira on that double heart.
That would have been nice.
Let's go blow up the donation machine.
Actually, two for one.
Totally worth.
Could have used Jira there, I guess, but...
Okay, at least this guy is easy.
We got it getting closer so our familiars can do something.
Whoa, how did I not get hit there?
I thought for sure I hit that flame.
Eyedrops, and we got a devil deal.
Definitely taking that.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, where are you?
Oh, there you are, I see.
Ha, he ran into the fire.
Nope.
Oh, the ocular rift, though, we gotta take that.
That's a must.
Copy's color.
Ah, I'll take both.
Yeah.
Why not?
Nothing else I want to do here, right?
No, wait, I have 12 coins.
I could potentially go back and buy something more from...
No, let's save it.
Saving it.
All right, it's not mom yet.
That's next floor.
Okay, now we're going to get a familiar.
It is a little chunky man.
I like it.
Ooh.
I have coins for that, but I need a bomb to get through.
Let's do this.
There's the bomb I need.
Yeah, I get sucked into the rift.
These guys have unpredictable movement.
It's worms.
The golden poop.
I actually didn't mean to do that, but I guess I...
I guess it's a good idea anyway.
I'm actually going to save this bomb just in case...
I'm sure I'll get another bomb, but...
It's getting a little dangerous.
Man, the rift really is helping me here with some DPS.
Ooh, dude, if I go in here, there's going to be two books.
That means we're going to get three out of three on Bookworm.
So Bible.
And this.
I got the little dice.
Necromonicon.
Cool.
Oh, wait, that's not the Bible.
Book of Revelations.
Plus one soul heart.
Activating replaces the floor boss with a Harbinger boss if possible.
Passively increases devil and angel room chances.
You know what?
Let's do it.
That sounds fucking funny.
Boom.
I have done it.
Bookworm.
Now I shoot more tears.
I think I want to keep this, maybe.
Passively increases devil and angel room chances.
I like that.
I need more deals.
Or I do this one.
Honestly, they're all kind of mediocre.
Yeah, they're not... I mean, I'm not excited by any of them, really.
Now, if it was an actual Bible...
I'm in the middle of something.
Wait, there's a dice room here.
What the...
Oh.
Drops one lit bomb per second for...
Maybe later.
Get sucked into the black hole.
That's right.
Get in there.
Fuck, I don't have a key.
Oh, goodness.
Okay, these rooms always look way more scary than they actually are.
Somehow, I always manage to do it without getting hit.
Man.
Keys.
Okay, that's nice.
I need to understand something again.
What if I do it again?
Let me do it twice.
But I need some more mana.
Oh, look at that!
The black hole power.
That was actually kind of underwhelming.
I thought everyone was going to die there.
Ah, but there we go.
Yeah.
Wait, I think they disappeared.
They didn't even get sucked into the hole.
I did it again.
Blow them up.
What a shot!
From downtown.
This way.
Oh my god, they're everywhere.
Just going to make a black hole.
Come on.
I need spaghettification!
Nice.
Oi, oi, oi.
Yeah, not bad.
Not bad.
So, the boss is here.
Oh, wait.
What about the dice room?
We got to check that out.
Hold on.
I can't do this yet.
I need to see the dice room.
If there's a six-sided dice in there...
I still don't have a key, dude.
What the hell is going on?
I may actually take the six-sided dice.
I know, I know.
It sounds crazy.
But I am not a big fan of my current setup.
I feel like anything else would be good right now.
Because look at my damage 2.62, man.
What the fuck is that shit?
Like, I'll take anything at this point.
Come on, mom.
I know you're not.
Done.
Now you're done.
Oh shit, this takes two keys.
Well, I guess I'm not doing that.
Never mind then.
There's other things I'd rather use my keys on.
Oh god, I'm stuck here!
Oh, I thought I could walk up there.
Oh, nothing?
Time to look for secret route.
I'm going to do it again.
Whoops.
I've done it three times now.
Wait.
I'm going to use this for the next room over here.
I guess we'll do it.
And there's the key.
I want to use it on the treasure room?
Oh man, treasure room or the coin room?
Both are pretty good.
I'm going to sacrifice some HP here.
What the hell is that?
Oh, it's a broken magnet.
Yeah, better than what I had.
Oh, right.
Wait, why is there a telephone in here?
Oh, that's what that is.
Ooh, hmm.
Shit, there are so many things I want to do.
I just don't have the resources.
What?
I didn't click!
I did not click the button, I swear to you.
But I guess I did.
Weird.
Wait!
Wait a damn minute now.
Check this out!
I'm going to go in here and shit all over the floor.
Wait, this could be a problem.
Yeah.
Bob Splatter!
He's not going to also piss all over the floor.
Placing a bomb also creates a small pool of high depth...
Why not?
Oh, it's a... no, I don't want it then.
Your old life lies in ruin.
Always your head in the...
I feel like that one is significant.
Always... something about heaven, maybe.
Always...
head in the clouds.
Maybe I bring a head somewhere.
Meet strangers without prejudice.
Can we not show that?
Thank you.
What do you want to do today?
Play Isaac!
Okay, I'm going to save the remaining money.
Man, I can't believe I wasted a bomb over here.
I could have blown up that machine just now.
Fuck!
I could have used this to get more bombs.
I'm going to go in here.
I'll save the money.
That is a Sister Maggie.
This is just all about the...
familiars today, huh?
Shit's not looking good.
I'll take that, I guess.
Come here.
Here we are.
Actually, I could do a bit of...
No, wait, there's no step.
War!
This guy is tough.
Oh no, this arena is going to fuck me.
Good thing I have familiars that help me.
Okay, good.
Clear out the arena.
There's a chest there.
But I don't have a bomb.
Did
that guy just...
He ran through the fires.
That's what you get for waging war.
Nobody wins.
Except me.
No, not this crab item.
Boo!
Guess we're leaving.
Wait, I want to change my...
Let's change the active, at least.
The thing is, though, if I don't find some damage, I think I'm forced to take the... what do you call it?
The Animal Farm book.
I forgot the name of it.
You know what I mean.
The one that spawns familiars.
It's like a good source of damage.
But I'm kind of curious about the other book.
I feel like there's got to be more to it, you know?
Do I have mana on this?
Oh, I don't know that it matters.
Reusable Soul... Oh, wait a minute.
It says reusable soul protection.
Hold on.
Look.
So, wait, wait, do I get a blue heart every time I use it?
Because I didn't notice that.
Maybe that is what's happening.
This needs more testing.
Man, I wish I had two keys.
I would have gone in there and...
licked that d6 so hard.
Please exchange all my items.
For something else.
Because I can't stand my setup.
Oops, I keep thinking that's the way to the boss.
Okay, this chest is unfortunate.
It's mom time, but I have no damage.
Fuck, I should have taken the monster manual.
Like, how am I gonna actually win the fight?
Oh, okay.
Drive by, the ultimate drive-by room.
It looks stupid, but it works.
And if it looks stupid and works, it ain't stupid.
Get sucked in!
Beautiful.
Oh, no.
Thank God the bird is out.
Oh, shit.
Focus.
Very nice, very nice, very nice.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck, I knew it was gonna happen.
I just knew it.
Don't take that heart.
Oh, fuck!
This room is killer.
Oh, the black hole was clutched there.
Wait, there's someone still alive.
Oh, there you are.
Oh, wait, I can't get in there.
Also, it does give me a blue heart.
Hell yeah.
I don't wanna gamble that.
I wanna find the shop.
Dude, imagine having backpack, this book, and converter.
That would be sick.
Oh, no, not these guys.
At least they're not lasering.
That's my saving grace right now.
Dude, I am tickling them.
Okay, black hole is good.
Okay, treasure room.
Technology two.
The thing is, though, this is gonna do no damage at all, right?
Like, there's so little damage in this one.
It's like poking someone with a spoon.
I need to see it in action.
Wait till you see me in action.
Wait, south.
Okay, I mean, okay, these guys are also very weak, so...
Yeah, it's not doing a lot, is it?
We gotta find some DPS, no, some damage now.
Damage items.
Okay, there's stuff.
I mean, the infinite range is gonna be the good thing here.
Okay, okay.
I'm scared of the laser.
Jesus!
Wow.
Come on, then.
Wait, I'm creating the black hole at the destination.
No, wait, am I?
No, I still have a tile, I think.
Yeah, I still have a tile, okay.
I thought I was creating it where the laser was, you know, impacting.
Which would have been kind of cool.
So, I have a lot of money.
Let's see.
Definitely that one.
Wait, wait, that's not what I think it is.
This is a different one.
Plus two keys.
Doubles the amount of pickups dropped by me.
Okay!
I thought it was the other key.
Doubles the effects of most active item.
Ooh!
That's very good for me.
And then we have...
All right.
There's still a glaring problem with this picture here, okay.
It doesn't even matter.
We need damage.
We have none.
The rift is gonna be the only source of damage right now.
Like, look at this, it's taking me forever to kill this guy.
No, no, look at that!
That spawned the black hole at the location!
Oh my god, you're kidding.
This is gonna be...
a very...
I don't even know what to call it.
It's gonna be a slog.
That's a good word for that.
At least the infant range here is a safety buffer, right?
That's good.
Open up!
Aw, man.
I can't believe I did that twice.
I think this is useless for me now, or...
Actually, I'm not sure how that would work.
Let's test it for a bit.
What a chest!
Have thou'st ever seen a chest as this?
Oh, I guess we have the double the chest thing, that makes sense now.
This is making sense.
Things are aligning as they should.
It's mount time.
I fucking pushed the bomb towards me!
I hate when that happens.
Ah, this is just messed up.
My familiars that are spawning here is my only source of damage.
The black holes are so helpful here.
And just the crowd control, you know?
Oh, mom's going crazy now.
Come on.
There we go.
Again?
Brother!
What the fuck are the chances of that?
Wait, is it actually good?
Let me see.
Taking damage with half or less red hearts.
Oh, wait a minute.
It allows access to higher stages.
Maybe that is what allowed me to do the thing I did last time.
Jumping into the chest.
But it says higher stages.
That would suggest going up and not down, right?
I don't know.
We gotta think about that.
We have one more active mana and then we can do another two hearts.
That's a great thing to look forward to.
There we go.
Dude, this is actually so good.
If we get some damage here, we're gonna be cooking hard.
Like, it's gonna be insane.
I just need a little bit.
It's not a lot.
I don't ask for much.
Just, I don't know.
Two more damage.
And I'm happy as a clam.
I don't need a lot.
Also, supremely low on keys.
But, what was it about this key?
What was the amount of pickups?
Okay, that's the chest one.
Goodbye, tomato.
Nice knowing ya.
Oh my god, will you die already?
Don't suck in my bombs.
Scary.
Okay,
keys are huge.
Oh my goodness, look at all this healing.
Can we step?
Perhaps we can step this time around.
I kinda wanna just go in.
Is that nuts?
Let's wait!
Who knows what we'll find?
That can maybe help us.
Oh yeah!
I'm taking that.
Huge.
And what's this?
Okay, that's fine.
That's okay.
I think it's a worthy trade.
Oh, there's a bomb.
Actually, wait.
Lovely.
Okay.
I hope there's a stepper on this stage.
Cause this would be the moment to do it.
Uh, plus two.
Oh, that's actually kinda big.
We're gonna use that on a boss.
Okay, there's three hands.
There's four hands!
Unless the third one or second one came back.
I think that's what that was.
Just gonna keep moving.
I take no chances here.
Not bad.
Fight room.
Oh, speed, that's actually also okay.
Or I mean, tears.
Oh, shit.
Not bad!
I have good crowd control, though.
More hearts for me.
Whoa, what is that lead?
Oh, it's the eye.
Laser versus laser.
That's cool.
I don't need range.
The devil, uh, plus two damage rights.
Like, look at his crowd control.
That is beautiful.
Man, stepping would be insane on this floor.
So much healing.
I don't think it's gonna happen.
I don't think we're gonna find one, unfortunately.
Like, I know these things.
I wish I had spectral tears, though.
That would help a lot.
Oh, that's nice.
Black hole on those little bastards.
Feels good, man.
Now, I can't get to those chests.
Man, that's so sad.
Chests are doubly as good right now.
Oh, wait, this is my friend over there.
Look at that stuff.
This is what happens when two black holes, or like four black holes, come very close to each other and start orbiting in space.
It's just a mess.
There we go.
Can I get two keys?
Wow.
Uh, well, we're done with this floor.
Surely next floor we're gonna have a stepper, right?
The Stairmaster will make an appearance.
Wait, I'm not even going the right way.
Depending on the boss we're gonna meet... oh, wait, we are gonna meet a special boss, aren't we?
Activating replaces the floor boss with a Harbinger... a Harbinger boss?
Is that like a category of bosses, or is it like one specific boss?
I guess we'll find out.
If it's the dude on the broomstick, like Harry Potter, we're gonna... we're gonna know.
If it's not, then we're gonna know.
In any case, we're gonna know.
Okay, so it's broomstick people.
Oh, wait, it is Harry Potter.
Okay, so... but it's different variations of Harry Potter's.
I'm surprised that the black hole is affecting this guy.
Whoa.
Okay, not too sh... uh, not this shitty item, dude.
Hold up, hold up, hold up, hold up!
That's the second one!
What's the difference?
Lock shot, contact, lock shot, deals contact, and fires charm... okay.
Maybe this is getting a little exciting now.
Alright, I like that.
Uh, what is that?
Black powder?
Leave behind a powder trail that spawns damaging pentagrams when circles are drawn?
Bombs have increased damage in size, shooting out fires will cause them to...
That sounds frickin' awesome.
So wait, really?
Dude, that is actually such a cool mechanic!
What?
That is dope as hell.
Um... yeah, movin' on.
It's like putting down traps.
Actually, I need to reread exactly what that pentagram does.
Is it like an IED?
It's just damaging, okay.
Damaging.
This guy wants hearts.
We could maybe give him that, actually.
Dude!
We get to one heart with this character!
It's perfect!
There's our damage!
Hahaha!
Ah, let's not waste all the money.
Actually, then again.
Maybe we should.
Because we're in the red spot, that means there's no shops anyway, so fuck it.
Oh, I didn't mean to.
Well...
That door is opened!
I didn't mean to draw a circle.
Pill?
Unidentified.
You know I'll be drinking that.
I don't want that.
Uh, okay.
More pills.
Holy recharge, Isaac's active item.
Hell yeah!
Ahoy!
And we can take this?
Oh my god.
I'm so ready to step.
Put me in the game, coach!
Actually take this and...
Uh...
Yeah?
Sure.
More bombs.
I want more pills.
I need pills.
Pill me!
Okay.
That means more for you.
Sp...
Hahaha!
Here, you have a friend now.
I hope you get along.
I'm actually gonna give him some money now.
I'm gonna blow you guys up then.
Maybe, maybe I'll come back actually first.
Yeah.
We could find more money.
Perhaps.
Oh, it makes such a big difference now.
I deal so much more damage.
Oh, we got laser bros and a lot of them.
Okay, so look, we're gonna take this now and go back.
Wait.
Did we...
We traded again or...
I'm confused about that.
I kinda wanna do this.
Oh, shit.
Alright, that went pretty well.
Oh, my God.
What the...
What is this movement?
Hahaha!
Wow!
Ranch fly...
Oh!
I like it.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, the black hole.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wait, does the black hole scale with my damage?
Please tell me it does.
Dealing contact damage to enemies.
It doesn't say that, but...
Maybe it does, you know?
Oh, wait, I shouldn't have taken that heart.
Actually, I should have, because now I'm gonna go back and...
Donate.
Oh, you bastard.
Man, the black hole even sucks in his projectiles.
It is just so good.
I also wanna find secrets.
There we go.
Now we have become the whore again.
Oh, wait, I keep forgetting I can make the circle thingies.
Wait, what is that?
Like, why can't I see what it is?
Tonsil.
After taking damage 6 to 12 times, spawn a Tonsil familiar that blocks shots.
After a second Tonsil is spawned, the trinket is destroyed.
Is that familiar gonna stay forever?
Like, it's not just for one floor, or...
Will this be triggered by this?
Because that's kinda crazy, if that's the case.
We can totally use that.
Um, I'm actually gonna get in here.
Should have made the bomb up here instead.
Just to test, you know, but it's fine.
Okay, go back again.
We're testing a bunch of things here.
I wanna see if the damage I take from interacting with this beggar is counting towards the thing I just got.
The Tonsil.
Look at all my familiars.
The whole army.
It's a movement.
We must have consumed almost all the pills by now, right?
Uh, there you go.
Too bad this effect doesn't stack, huh?
So every time I get down to one, it stacks up.
That would be crazy.
Give
me that, and now we move on.
Whoa, holy flies!
Look at the way they're orbiting the back hole!
Amazing.
Or the rift, I should say.
It's more like a wormhole.
Maybe they pop out somewhere else on another floor.
Uh, spawn a pile of slowing black creep.
No thanks.
Can I use the flight somewhere?
I wanna use it for something.
I guess I can use it to get in there.
That means if I go in there now, I'm gonna...
Oh, actually, hold on.
This is getting a little too risky, I think.
No, no, we're gonna use loose blue hearts.
It's totally fine.
We're chilling.
Oh, and wait, we have the wafer!
Hey!
Obviously.
The pact!
Tears and damage!
Yeah!
Amazing!
Definitely taking that.
And now we're gonna do this.
Oh!
I misunderstood how that worked, then.
I thought it worked in the following way.
When you enter for the first time with flight, you don't take damage.
But then you do take damage on the way out, because you already took damage.
But I thought if you go in and not take damage, and then you fly out again, you're not gonna take damage.
Well, that's not the case.
I'm gonna blow all this up.
Fuck!
I could have used flight here!
Oh, it doesn't matter.
That was amazing.
That was so much stuff in that gist.
This looks like a secret.
Oh, the button.
That was a fun room.
Well, I think...
Oh, we have one more room to go.
And then we're gonna go to boss.
Yeah, that's the plan.
Actually, hold on.
We grab this half heart.
Where is it?
There it is.
We're gonna donate a little bit more to the beggar.
Just a bit.
In fact, twice.
We're gonna do this two more times.
And then we're gonna blow them up.
Dark matter!
Fuck yeah.
Amazing.
Now we're gonna grab the full heart.
No, we're not actually.
Are we?
No, we're not, because then we lose the effect here.
Time to go to the room down here.
I can't believe I never explored that room, actually.
It's right next to the arcade.
Wait, this guy is a special boss.
Champion type dude, I think.
I tried to push it last minute there.
Oh no, wait, I'm putting a debuff on them.
I'm putting the skull on them.
What is that debuff?
I need to see this.
It is fear, right?
It's gotta be fear.
Be afraid of me.
Yeah, it is going pretty well.
Something I wonder, though.
If I were to get more base damage from an item, and I then get turned into a whore.
Is it like straight up double damage?
Because we have 4.39 damage now, and before we had something 2 point, you know.
Because that means this could really snowball if we get some more damage from items.
Wait, this way.
How do I... Oh, down here.
It lives.
Dude, the black holes are gonna be so good here.
Look at that.
He has no projectiles.
I'm just gonna drink my coffee, guys.
I'm playing with one hand right now.
Going pretty well, I'd say.
Oh, shit.
Okay, we can move.
Very nice.
Okay.
Go.
We are moving on to the cathedral.
To the church house.
I wanted to go down.
I was on autopilot.
I was gonna go to Sheol.
I'm so stupid.
Oh my god.
Whatever.
I had one job.
I was on mega autopilot just now.
There's too many hearts.
There's something you rarely hear.
Dude, the rift with this technology thingy is too much fun.
A bomb spawn.
Or an item.
Okay, so let's see here.
Spawn's a large bomb.
Nope.
Nah.
I'm just gonna start looking for secrets immediately.
I have so many bombs.
Yes, we're gonna black hole over here.
Oh, I keep forgetting to make pentagrams on the floor.
Let's do that.
What happened?
I'm slowed.
Oh, you can make a massive wait.
What's with the timer?
What's happening with the timer?
Okay, fuck the pentagram.
Kill this guy.
Okay, there we go.
That was a bit of a mess.
Dude, I betcha there's some kind of secret.
Where if you make a pentagram in a certain room, something happens.
Maybe the room with the bed.
Let's make a pentagram around...
Oh wait, we can't walk around the bed though.
But you know what I mean, right?
Like some room where you make a pentagram.
Like maybe here, you see the circle?
I don't think it's here, but somewhere like that.
I'm calling it.
Oh, I thought I had to move out of the red area on the floor.
I'm wow-brained, you know.
Get out of the red.
That is a question mark, I am curious.
Two spades, that's bombs, isn't it?
No, it's keys, okay.
Let's make a circle here.
Oh, he's dead.
Circle on this guy.
Oh, it doesn't do that much damage, does it?
This is so demon.
Speed down, no thanks.
What's happening?
Jar people!
Kinda wanna get in there.
Actually, I don't want to.
Look at that, that's beautiful.
Fan-freaking-tastic.
Gonna blow you up.
Dude, I kinda wanna get, like, angel rooms.
I'm getting kinda tired of the devil rooms.
I need to not take devil rooms, so I can get angel rooms.
Next time we're doing that.
Black Hole is so freaking good.
It's maybe one of my favorite items now.
Especially with the technology, the way it spawns on the enemy is actually just so good.
Threading the needle there.
Yo, what is happening?
Oh, is this guy shielding?
Crazy, what a crazy run.
There's the boss.
I think we're just gonna go in.
Actually, we're not.
Because if there's more after this, we gotta be ultra ready.
Last time I wasn't.
Who knows what we're gonna find down here?
Or up here, I mean.
Oh, tomato.
There's another room over here we missed.
We can have some coins.
Actually, you know what?
I'm gonna save my coins, because I don't know what's coming next.
The next floor after this?
Kinda looked like...
We may be able to buy something.
It was like wooden floors and shit.
Let's check.
But first we gotta defeat this guy.
We can't, you know...
Oh my...
The black hole.
No, I mean, okay.
The gravitational effect is astounding.
It is absolutely beautiful.
Yeah, suck him in!
We had a brief lapse there in black hole uptime, so we can't have that happen again.
Yeah, suck him all in.
Flawless, flawless.
So now, if we jump in...
Let's see if it actually happens again.
Ooh!
Okay!
It's like a guaranteed thing, I guess.
Very nice.
Let's see what this is all about!
Wait, it's...
We're inside a chest!
Mind blown!
That's what it said!
Lord!
Oh, wait a minute!
I've been on two hearts for a while, I should've been on one heart!
I don't want that.
Hot bombs!
Plus five bombs.
Place the bombs, deal contact damage to enemies.
Isaac's bombs, explosion's deep behind, fires to damage enemies, block enemy shots, grants immunity to damage from state...
Alright!
I like it!
Play-doh, cookie, shirt.
Butt bombs!
The concussed man, my bombs are gonna be strong.
But also against me.
Guess we're exploring this?
Oh my god!
We need gravitational effects stats!
And we need to somehow get rid of some red hearts!
This is the next thing on the agenda.
Dude, the ice effects are legitimately gonna be pretty good.
Okay!
Get stuck in my potential!
Uh-oh.
Woah!
The army is coming!
Holy fucking shit!
Let's make a pentagram.
The seven seals has appeared!
Whatever that is.
Sounds cool, though.
Dude, this is so exciting!
Oh wait, that's dangerous.
Wait, it's also the enemy's bombs that turn into my modified bombs, it seems.
We need to become a whore.
Oh, I can't see nothing.
Here's a bomb for you.
Another bomb!
Oh my god, what the...
Daddy long legs!
I guess I got to meet that dad.
Suck on my penta.
Until I ram.
Oh, I shouldn't stay still.
Keep moving.
And we got a key for that.
I have a feeling this is gonna get pretty insane.
Yeah, sock them all in, sock them all in!
Get out of there!
He puked on himself.
Disgusting.
Oh, yo, yo, yo.
Dude, they're going crazy.
They have no chill.
Yeah!
That with the wafer?
Man, I am a tank.
And I'm rich.
And I'm successful.
And I'm hot.
Yeah!
See ya, sir.
Oh!
Wait, I don't have a trinket?
How the fuck do I not have a trinket?
This way.
Uh, two green people.
I need to slow those projectiles down.
Just like that.
Get stuck in my potential.
Yeah.
Give me your money.
Dude,
I wonder if we get a shot here.
Imagine.
We should, though, right?
Like, the chest is all related to items and materialism.
Please let it be.
See ya.
Fool.
Better than what I had.
Why is he shooting that way?
Oh, because a lot of my familiars, maybe.
Oh, God.
On Bilgle Court?
When entering a room with half a red heart or less, gain a little Steven Familia that fires homing tears.
Dude, I kind of want to get to half a red heart.
That would be perfect.
Better than a chance of taking damage to spawn a Gemini Familia.
Man, how do I get my red hearts down?
I need to find, like, a beggar or something.
What other ways can I do it?
Do I have one lit bomb per second?
Nah.
Come on, potential!
There we go.
We caught him.
Oh.
Where you going?
Oh, you're over there.
Oh, my God.
Gerties.
It's Gertie's parents!
I'm so sorry, Mini Gertie.
I have to do it.
Self-defense.
Dude, what is the fucking boss gonna be?
What?
Hold on, I'm not ready.
We gotta fully explore this place.
Who knows when we'll be back here.
I gotta see, man.
We gotta also try and look for secrets.
A-ha-ha!
Speak enough!
Pills!
Orbital!
Uh, sure.
And, sure.
Okay, let's see here.
Okay, we have a room here.
Yeah, they're both in my potential now.
Love to see it.
Oish.
That was a fast jump.
So, this is the starting room, right?
The Lard.
Oh, God.
I'm not going anywhere.
Uh, surely here, no?
I'm gonna keep bombing the shit out of this.
This could be the last stage, you know?
I don't know.
Mmm, okay.
That's a suspicious room.
Nothing.
That one I checked, I think?
You gotta be kidding me.
Uh, okay, fine.
Let's check out the boss.
Let's see what we got.
Actually, uh, did I check this?
I guess my bombs are pretty wild.
I should be using that against the boss.
What?
We're fighting freaking BB!
There's a bomb for you.
There's another bomb for you.
You like bombs?
Where you going, son?
You can fly, huh?
Does that mean you're an angel?
Are you an angel?
Okay!
That wasn't even hard.
BB ain't shit.
Okay, here we go.
We keep jumping!
Oh!
He's not Italian.
Daughter?
They hated me, they loved her!
That died?
Or left for milk or something?
The end, yeah, but is it?
At this point, I don't fucking believe you.
You cry wolf one more time?
Oh, new song.
No, it's the same, okay.
Okay, so, mom and dad had a boy and a girl, my sister.
They loved her so much that they disregarded me.
They locked me in my room and they hated me.
And then dad left for milk and it was just the three of us.
And maybe, I don't know what happened to the daughter, but something happened.
Or, that was me and I just had a fancy hairstyle for that one moment in time.
It was one of the blunder years, I don't know.
Something like that.
Sacrificial dagger, you are my challenge.
The angels, wait!
Okay.
Ooh, wait!
Wait, is it actually...
Look at this!
So, I fought me and then I fought...
BB.
Wait, so this guy...
I6 starts with the D6?
Dude, I'm fucking crazy!
If that is the same D6 I had...
You gotta be kidding.
Unlocked by beating something that I didn't do yet.
Unlocked by beating heart mode...
Okay, this one, we can do that, I think.
Like, at this point, we have what it takes.
Well...
Look at that, twisted horns.
That was a short one.
A nice and sweet session with a lot of wins and a lot of good times.
Wasn't that nice?
What's up, guys?
Are we chilling?
Dude, are we just having some amazing sessions lately?
Yeah, that was a crazy combination of items there.
Wafer, and then we had the...
Oh, I forgot what the name is, but the one that...
The one I got at the end, you know?
Yeah, and the revelations, crazy combos.
Crazy combos.
Yeah, Book of Revelations.
Good job on 100%ing the game.
Thank you, Veena Bumter.
Why haven't you streamed that much lately?
Have you seen my streams, though?
I've been streaming quite a bit lately.
Do you have a playlist of music that you play?
Yeah, I do.
I have a whole list of plays.
No, I don't stream constantly.
I stream on average, I would say, every second day.
Maybe sometimes every third day, it depends.
In, like, two days or three days, I gotta go to my parents for a bit, so...
No streams in that period.
I'll try and get another stream in for sure before that, though.
I actually can't share the playlist because it is...
Like, it's local.
Local files.
The music that I have in this playlist is, like, a little bit remixed by myself...
to make it loop perfectly, you know?
So it's not as easy... I guess I could tell you which songs they are, but yeah.
Do more of Seizel.
Yeah, the cool thing about... Do more of Seizel next?
Okay, you got it, man!
Someone's asking for a Seizel I oblige.
You got it!
That's all you had to say, fam!
We love a Seizel here, yes?
Oh yeah, a Seizel speedrun, true!
We're gonna do that.
I did promise that.
Or, I didn't promise it, but I did say I was gonna do it.
Wait, are you actually named a Seizel?
I didn't catch that.
Oh, Loki, Loki, thank you for gifting subs.
Are you the boss by any chance that I have encountered a couple times in this game?
Is that a reference to that?
Or is it the Norse god you're talking about?
Oh, Loki with two eyes, that's true, yeah.
A little different.
Absolutely no tilt to stream.
Right?
I think it's because I'm getting better at the game, and I'm starting to realize that I have more options in any given situation.
And I also got a little lucky with drops today.
And that's a good, you know, cocktail of happenstances.
Did you play Isaac with d6 next stream?
Yeah, if the RNG gods allow me to, I'm gonna spin the wheel.
I will throw the dice, and then we'll see if it lands on 6.
This was a good spacebar learning stream?
I mean, dude, I was, what do you call it, fiending for that spacebar.
I was constantly looking at my mana.
When is the next?
Like, I can't get enough of the spacebar with this item.
I think I only saw you stream one day last week.
No, that's not true.
I streamed at least three days last week.
I know you probably get this a lot, but these starting soon screens are always a work of art.
No, I can't really take that compliment, because I didn't make this.
But it's just a combination.
It's more like I took things that already exist, and I just make a composition of it.
I didn't write this stuff, you know?
I'm basically like someone who compositions already existing stuff.
That's the extent, because I can't do art.
I can't draw, you know?
Any new notes after today?
Yeah, Book of Revelations is an amazing sauce, and we're always gonna pick it.
And I think I like the black hole even more after today.
Especially with technology, too.
Or whatever that was called.
Oh yeah, the card pattern, yeah.
Combined with Revelations, oh my.
That was just a beautiful combo.
The glitch starting soon was cool.
Well, I did that because the last one before that was the glitched run, you know?
I thought it was fitting.
I didn't want to keep it all the time.
Svarios?
Are you a bot?
What's going on with you, man?
What's happening here?
He's blue for an amazing reason?
Done for today?
Yeah, we just ended.
I had some amazing runs.
Dude, did I win every single run today?
No, I lost one.
The first one, because we got blue boy.
And it didn't go very well.
It was the first run, and it went horribly.
That was a disaster.
Yeah, a warm-up run, exactly.
Oh yeah, and Eve, true.
Yeah, yeah.
Wait, Eve was the one we just had, wasn't it?
Unless I'm smoking something.
Eve is the whore, yeah.
Yep, yep.
Play some greed, too.
There's so many things I want to do.
Like, we'll get to that.
I'm going to play all of it, don't worry.
I'm also going to do more challenges.
I know I keep saying it, but I will do it, trust me.
I'm just getting distracted by awesome things that I want to do first.
And I keep discovering new shit, right?
So I think this is cool.
Are you liking Isaac so far?
What do you think, Smeek?
Just based on my reactions and if you've seen any of my streams.
I think the answer to that is pretty obvious.
Yes, I like it.
The angel awaits Oliver.
I know.
We got to get to the angels.
It's been way too demon lately.
We got to make it more angel.
Right?
I can't wait to see an angel.
Hope we can see an angel next time.
Oh, and... step my foot, I can't stop.
We need to engage on that.
I've just been unlucky with the floors that I wanted to do it on, where there was no step.
That's horrible.
I'm trying to step all the time, you know?
Because I'm so intrigued by the keys I get from that.
I can't stop thinking about it.
Exactly.
No demon deal next time?
We'll see.
It depends.
I mean, you got to be able to adapt right to the situation.
I sound like Bear Grylls over here out in the wild.
But yeah, we're going to see how it goes, you know?
You got to live off the land and improvise.
I Ching.
Spike's tread on me, daddy.
Exactly.
That one.
I will bend the game to my will.
I think I'm slowly doing that.
Also, please do realize the converter sucks?
That's just like your opinion, man.
I think it rocks.
Fight me.
The converter is frickin' goated.
It is the greatest.
It is unbelievable how every time I get that, everything goes well.
Convert your opinion, man.
Nope.
I will never do that.
Please realize the Zazel sucks.
Okay, you guys are just gaslighting me.
It's like people in the comments section lately on YouTube.
Zazel is also goated.
But imagine, a Zazel with converter.
The ultimate combo.
Doesn't get better than that, baby.
That's when things really start to pick up.
Oh, yeah.
That's when it goes really fast all of a sudden.
That's when you start winning a lot and, you know, the speedometer goes to 200.
And it's just going faster and it's going faster and faster and faster.
And then all of a sudden we're taking a turn.
It's going the other way.
Oh, my God.
No.
Okay, let's not do that.
Come back here.
Hey, thank you, Pablo.
Thank you for subscribing with your Prime.
15 months!
I appreciate it.
Pablo3621.
So, converter, Guppy's paw, school bag and sharp plug is infinite.
I don't even know what sharp plug is, dude.
School bag, I know what it is.
Guppy's paw, I've heard of.
Converter, I think I know that one.
I mean, converter is good.
You just need to know when it's time to convert and when it's time to hold.
I always convert.
If in doubt, you convert.
It's really simple, really.
That's why the item is so good.
You don't have to think, you just convert.
Convert, convert, convert.
Thank you, Smeagol.
Appreciate the Prime.
And yes, I called you Smeagol.
That's what I think of.
You are now forever branded a Smeagol in my mind.
Yeah, no bag sitting, please.
Thanks, Santi.
Don't forget to shout convert like it's your anime alt.
Dude, I actually... I think I understand what you mean by that sentence.
But I've never actually watched an anime where they do an alt.
You know what I mean?
Because I know like Pokemon has these sort of... where...
you know, the lasers meet in the middle and they go like...
And all these explosions happen and slow... like I've never seen that sort of stuff.
Never.
I think the closest to it is probably Persona 5.
And I don't even think that's very close to that stuff.
Maybe a bit.
Give me the controller.
Mom said it's my turn.
No!
I'm done for now.
You can have it.
There better not be any grease on it like last time, though, when I get it back.
It better be in pristine condition.
Who's my second favorite character?
It's Azul.
Ah, okay.
Let me be real.
So favorite is Azul.
Second favorite...
Well, if it sounds... if it is as good as it sounds right now, and I haven't even tried it yet...
It's gotta be Isaac.
Like, just based... if he actually starts with the fucking D6...
Then I'm like, whoa.
Hello.
What's going on right now?
You know?
Like, we gotta do that.
Gotta get in there.
The D6...
My mind was blown when it worked on... on the one-armed thief.
Next time I'm gonna try to unlock the thing with Lazarus.
Well, you complete it without losing life, I think.
Because that unlocks a new character, and I want to try that.
That's gotta be on the list.
I'm actually gonna write it now.
So don't forget.
Play... uh... Lazarus to unlock a new character.
And hopefully it'll go better than last time I tried it.
Because that was kind of a shit show.
You can only go up from now, though.
Do a flip.
But that... that makes it a flip-flop... a flip-show, then.
Also, S.H.I.E.L.D.
Please don't autopilot.
I know!
I... I was autopil... I said I was gonna go to S.H.I.E.L.D.
And then I was just like... I see the light, I go to it, you know?
Blowing crown insane.
You had it today, but it was off most of the time.
Yeah, that's true.
True?
But it was... it was so insane at first when I had the character, and then I was like, aww.
Because my tears were so low, and I shot one tear every minute, you know?
Felt really bad.
All in all, though, it's good.
It's a good item.
Alright, I'm out of here.
Thanks for watching, people.
Thank you for subscribing and hanging out and following and just, you know, being so nice in the chat.
I really appreciate it.
You guys are the best.
And have a wonderful Tuesday.
Ciao!